a gate control and electrical tape
I will teach you how to sell paçoca fratello
learn
tamo together
really like
hi all good
sorry to go in like this with the anklet
I just won an open semi
but it's soft
I used to sell a business to make money
very good and highly addictive
but how much I took money
I bought the cargo here and wanted to see if you like it.
oh that it is very good and highly addictive
that are my panties
for only two reais
meant this is control
from home
gate i put a tape
just so we can undertake and I accept pix too
just be careful the police are there bro
is ha ha
only my paçoquinhas
is on
for only two reais
it's here
here oh that bro
tamo together
the other self-addicting paçoca
only my paçoquinhas
tamo together
I'll get it here man
I've already made a qr code here or it's on
ai ai
this one is the best paçoquinha you can taste
my brother is on
when the police can't let them see this asshole here
thank you brother
stay with god there
tamo together
thank you
six account
for only two reais
next to home
put the crazy one in here
I'm playing with you
I don't know what I have in my head to do these things
born
my paçoquinhas is on
instagram
thank you brother
tamo together hand
it's worth it
so much that I got some money down there
I put the load here
wanted to know if they are comfortable
just be careful there are police passing by
and highly addictive that are my panties
control from the gate house
I was never even arrested
unarmed female
nairobi
today was day six
i have thirty days to set up a business
if you want to know how far this will go
accompany me there
until tomorrow